Mitchell Kabenda

Phone: 515-724-8861 | Email: Mstacy.kabenda@gmail.com

Summary

5 years - Behavioral Health

5 years - Multi-discipline Strategy Management

5 years - Adult & Pediatric Psychiatry & Advocacy

6 years - Leadership & Collaboration

1.5 years Software Development

Relevant Projects

Neolth Stress Management Tool

March 2024 - Current

UX Design and Front-End Development

★ Building user Interface through the use of figma to create wireframes and clickable prototype

Mental Health Website JWT Authentication

March 2024 - May 2024

Full-Stack

- Technology Stack: Utilizing Django for backend development and React.js for frontend interface, Javascript, Python,
- Features: Implementing user registration, login, and protected routes for data security.
- User Experience: Prioritizing a seamless and intuitive user interface for enhanced usability.

Relevant Professional Experience

Neolth

March 2024 - Current

Digital Mental Health Ambassador and Intern

- Collaborating with a team to develop innovative digital solutions in mental health care, with a focus on prevention and education for college-level students, while aligning company objectives with user design needs to ensure seamless user
- Applying the CDIO methodology to plan, design, implement, to assist with the operation of a digital solution.
- Crafting comprehensive product timeline and roadmap to assist in strategically guiding the project progression and milestone achievement

Techstars

October 2023 - February 2024

Marketing & Promotions Lead

- Led targeted social media marketing strategy & campaigns via LinkedIn, X, Instagram.
- Managed ecosystem growth via newsletter maintenance, communicating with >1000 subscribers & 500 strategic stakeholders.
- Communicated marketing materials with strategic partnerships with: Des Moines Business Record, Greater Des Moines Partnership, One Million Cups, Innovation Iowa, & University of Iowa JPEC.
- Engaged acquisition channels & vielded ~100 orders w/ 100+ ticket resulting > \$1k in ticket revenue

Professional Experience

UnityPoint Health - Behavioral Health Services; Inpatient Pediatrics

October 2023 - Current

Behavioral Health Counselor

- Facilitate weekly psychoeducational groups focused on Adolescent Mental Health, Self, & Personal development.
- Provide weekly counseling, monitoring & management of ten patients
- Enable the safety, & well-being of patients through the use of de-escalation techniques & safety planning strategies
- Via patient check-ins & progress evaluations, confirmed to have improved the well-being & stability of ~90 patients

University of Iowa - Behavioral Health Services; Adult Psychiatry

July 2022 - July 2023

Psychiatric Nursing Assistant

- Recorded patient health data into the EPIC system for EHR management.
- Assisted in the delivery of emergency Adult, Pediatric, & Geriatric Psychiatry patient care & service.
- Assisted with Pediatric, Adult, Geriatric, & Emergency departments, defusing over 100 patients monthly

Nisaa African Family Services

July 2019 - January 2022

Youth Advocate

- Planned & led 10+ sessions that educated our ecosystem of young African members on Sexual Assault, Mental Health, & Domestic Violence across NISSA's Iowa footprint.
- Spearheaded, & executed NISSA's digital strategy & engaged 1000s of African Students
- Led NISSA's Gala of 100s of attendees across 5 successful events & performances each year.

Education

Bachelor of Science; Global Health Studies | University of Iowa

- Student Government Senator | Health & Equity, & Diversity & Inclusion Committees
- NAACP Youth Council President | Mental Health & Wellness Committee
- African Student Association | Co-Treasurer
- Black Campus Ministries | Co-President

Associate of Arts; Liberal Arts | Des Moines Area Community College

Associate of Science; General Studies|Des Moines Area Community College

Meta Blueprint; Front End Developer Certification | Meta Technologies

Gained proficiency in HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Reactjs, Figma, Bootstrap

Meta Blueprint; Back End Developer Certification | Meta Technologies

• Gained proficiency in Django, Python, VS Code, Git, Bootstrap, GitHub

Google Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design | Google Inc

Wireframe, user experience design, User experience, User Interface Design, figma, prototype, UX Research, Web Design

Relevant Achievements

Iowa City TechStars Startup Weekend

★ Earned 3rd place for creating an executable Al-powered Mental Health model focused on adolescents.

University of Iowa Tippie School of Business Startup Weekend

★ Earned 2nd place by creating an executable Software Application focused on identity verification & validation on dating apps.